This is number three of my five favorite
buy-for-life items. This is the
Leuchtturm Journal. I would say [music]
that this product probably has the
highest cost-benefit ratio in this
entire list. It costs maybe $20 for a
branding journal, but it has given me so
much back in terms of being able [music]
to track my habits, track my thoughts,
and also achieve my goals. I've used it
for 10 years now, [music] and when I go
back to my first journal, it still is in
really good condition, and I have no
doubt that it can continue to last for
the next few decades. [music] And this
is contrasted with some of the cheaper
notebooks that I've tried with cheaper
paper. A lot of times the pen will bleed
into the paper over many years, and it
becomes sort of not legible, [music]
but that hasn't really been the case
with these journals. Every journal that
I have, I also make some modifications
to it, so I added [music] this pen loop
to the back so I can put my pen right
here. Also, I have an AirTag in case I
lose it.